Shreshtha **Gupta**

Wealth Manager

contact 07874915759 London, United Kingdom

Summary

I graduated from Imperial Business School with Masters in Science in Investment and Wealth Management. I have previously worked in MKU and Horiba as finance intern. My core competencies are -

- Writing technical reports on stock markets and equities
- Analysis of ETFs in Europe and Asia markets. I have worked in HYSE, NSE and NASDAQ.

Experience

2017 - 2018 ETFGI

London, United Kingdom

Research Assistant

I graduated from Imperial Business School with Masters in Science in Investment and Wealth Management. I have previously worked in MKU and Horiba as finance intern. My core competencies are -

- Writing technical reports on stock markets and equities
- Analysis of ETFs in Europe and Asia markets. I have worked in HYSE, NSE and NASDAQ.
- · Bring coffee for Debbie

2014 - 2015 MKU Pvt. Ltd.

Kanpur, India

Finance Intern

- I graduated from Imperial Business School with Masters in Science in Investment and Wealth Management. I have previously worked in MKU and Horiba as finance intern. My core competencies are Writing technical reports on stock markets and equitie
- Analysis of ETFs in Europe and Asia markets. I have worked in HYSE, NSE and NASDAQ.

Education

2016 - 2017 **MSc**, Finance

Imperial Business School

GPA: Distinction

I graduated from Imperial Business School with Masters in Science in Investment and Wealth Management. I have previously worked in MKU and Horiba as finance intern. My core competencies are -

- · Writing technical reports on stock markets and equities
- Analysis of ETFs in Europe and Asia markets. I have worked in HYSE, NSE and NASDAQ.

2012 - 2015 Bachelors of Finance, BFM

HR College of Commerece

GPA: 6.95

I graduated from Imperial Business School with Masters in Science in Investment and Wealth Management. I have previously worked in MKU and Horiba as finance intern. My core competencies are -

- · Writing technical reports on stock markets and equities
- Analysis of ETFs in Europe and Asia markets. I have worked in HYSE, NSE and NASDAQ.

Awards

2014 Company Secratary, ICSI

Completed Company Secretary certificate course from ICSI

2015 Member, Finance Society

Worked for Finance society as a Treasurer and organised events.

· Organized college level equity trading competition

· Collected funds for society through alumni

Skills

Analysis: DCF and Financial Modelling, Excel programming

Technical: Python, VBA, Excel, MATLAB

Languages

Fluent Proficiency: Hindi, English

Working Proficiency: Spanish, French

Limited Proficiency: Japanese